Information



Name: Egor Tomashin

Gender: male

Birthdate: 26.05.2000

Phone number: +79166163090

Email: tomashined@mail.ru, tomashined@gmail.com

Location: <u>Russia, Moscow region, Povarovo</u> Citizenship: <u>Russia, ready for relocation</u>

Education

University: Moscow Polytechnic University

Period: 2018 - to the present (bachelor's degree until 2022)

Department: Institute of printmedia and information technologies

Specialty: 09.03.02 Information systems and technologies

Specialization: Augmented and virtual reality technologies in the media industry

Desired positions

Project Manager

Game Designer

Unity Developer

Work experience

Organization	NDA
Region	Russia
Period	January 2021 to the present
Work type	Permanent and full-time work
Position	Middle Unity Developer
Responsibilities	Game development

Organization	Magic Quick, https://magicquick.me/
Region	New York, USA (remotely)
Period	April 2020 to the present
Work type	Project work
Position	Unity AR Game Developer
Responsibilities	Development of parts of future educational games and applications in augmented reality for mobile devices.

Organization	FIRGAMESUS (Egor Tomashin), https://firgamesus.ru/
Region	Povarovo, Russia
Period	September 2018 – to the present

Work type	Project work
Position	Project Manager & Game Designer & Unity Developer
Responsibilities	Development of games and apps for mobile platforms (simple and with AR and VR) on Unity Engine with C#. It is my "studio", on behalf of which I publish my personal projects.

Organization	GOLDFINCHWORKS, https://goldfinchworks.ru/
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	December 2020
Work type	Project and temporary work
Position	Unity Developer
Responsibilities	Development of VR simulators for the industry on HTC Vive Focus Plus
Dismissal	It was a temporary work

Organization	Earworm Studio, http://earworm.studio/
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	September 2020 – November 2020
Work type	Full-time
Position	Unity Game Developer
Responsibilities	Game development for various platforms such as Android (Google Play and UDP) and WebGL (Russia social networks) on Unity with C#.
Dismissal	By agreement of the parties, because of crisis

Organization	AdStarter
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	July 2020 – September 2020
Work type	Full-time
Position	Unity Developer
Responsibilities	Apps development for publishing to Google Play with WebView.
Dismissal	Move to game studio.

Organization	GTA 5 RP: Grand Role Play
Region	https://gta5.grand-rp.su/
Period	March 2020 - June 2020
Work type	Part-time
Position	Game admin, Tester
Responsibilities	Monitoring compliance with game rules on the server, communicating with players, inventing various activities and entertainment for them.

Dismissal	By choice, the need to grow as a programmer.
-----------	--

Organization	TV Channel TNT (Internet Department), https://vk.com/tnt
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	October 2019
Work type	Temporary work
Position	Coordinator, Community manager
Responsibilities	- coordination of community subscribers for effective "fight" in VK Pixel Battle 2019
	- search for allies among other teams
	- Organization of places of communication
	- creation of graphic materials
	- final collection of ID of all participants for further awarding

Organization	Liga Robotov, https://obraz.pro/
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	February 2019 – April 2019
Work type	Part-time
Position	Teacher of programming for children and teenagers
Responsibilities	Teaching visual programming to children and teenagers in Scratch and LEGO MINDSTORMS.
Dismissal	Due to the delay of salaries

About me

I am Egor from Russia, 20 years old. I am ready to move to another country with relocation support, but because of current epidemiological situation I prefer remote work at first time. At the moment, I am studying in the 3rd year at the University (Moscow Polytech), but it is not a hindrance for full-time work because of it is good when student works.

I develop games and apps for Android (Google Play, UDP), IOS (App Store), WebGL (social networks). Because of specialization "AR and VR technologies in the media industry" I also can create projects int AR/VR/MR formats (Google VR, ARFoundation, HTC Vive, etc.).

I started my "life" in GameDev with development in Unity + C#, making my personal projects from scratch to release. So, during this time, I managed to test myself in many positions – Project Manager, Game Designer, etc.

You can view my project portfolio on my website.

Professional skills

- Five-year experience in GameDev, but hard experience is less
- Optimal knowledge of Unity + C# and programming principles

- Projects for various platforms and formats
- Integrating different plugins
- Coding in JavaScript and PHP for WebGL projects
- Work with software from Adobe, Microsoft, Google, Autodesk
- Ability to manage teams and projects
- Writing GDD & documentation
- Native Russian, Intermediate English (B1)

Additional contacts

LinkedIn	https://vk.me/tomashined
Telegram	https://t.me/tomashined
WhatsApp	89166163090
Skype	live:tomashined
LinkedIn	https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomashined/